[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Malek_s02_01",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHands",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Marauder",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Marauder_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Malek_s02_01",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHands",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Syndicate",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Syndicate_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Malek_s02_01",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHands",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sadiki_s02_01",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 2,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_BloodoftheSand_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_WordofaThief",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_Ring",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_WordofaThief_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_HardBoiled",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_1hTowerShield",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_HardBoiled_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_SatyrFlute",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumFeet",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_SecondThoughts_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_FalseProfits",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
  "ItemRewardQty": 40,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_FalseProfits_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_EggHunt",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Zander_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_2hFireStaff",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_EggHunt_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_06",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumLegs",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_07",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_1hSword",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_EmptyNest",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Rima_s02_04",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_11",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumHead",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_EmptyNest_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Sharif_s02_11",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_12",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_11",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_MediumChest",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_13",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_12",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_2hGreatsword",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_S02_Remembrance",
  "Type": "SeasonQuest",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Grace_s02_02",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Main_14",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_13",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "House_HousingItem_Season2_SandwormEgg_Variant3",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_S02_Remembrance_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_T1_RiseoftheBeast_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Phaedra_s02_01",
  "AchievementId": "95A_Trial_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_14",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "s02_Quest_2hBow",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_T01_RiseoftheBeast_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero",
  "Type": "Journey",
  "DifficultyLevel": 60,
  "Task": "95A_S02_T2_RiseoftheHero_Container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "95A_Phaedra_s02_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Trial_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Success",
  "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
  "ItemRewardQty": 1,
  "Repeatable": "TRUE",
  "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
  "Title": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Title",
  "Description": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Start_Prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "95A_T02_RiseoftheHero_Obj_Complete",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE"
 }
]